const DATA = [
  {
    question: 'Who was the "first" Avenger?',
    answers: [
      'Iron Man',
      'Hulk',
      'Captain America',
      'Thor'
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Captain America',
  },

  {
    question: 'What does S.H.I.E.L.D. stand for?',
    answers: [
      'Systematic Hyper International Energy and Linguistics Divison',
      'Strategic Homeland Intervention Enforcement and Logistics Division',
      'Secret Hub of Investigative Evidence at Denver',
      'Strength Hope Imagination Empathy and Doing',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Strategic Homeland Intervention Enforcement and Logistics Division',
  },

  {
    question: 'Which infinity stone was first introduced in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?',
    answers: [
      'Space Stone',
      'Time Stone',
      'Mind Stone',
      'Soul Stone',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Space Stone',
  },

  {
    question: 'In what city did Loki attack earth in \"Avengers\" ?',
    answers: [
      'Washington D.C.',
      'Chicago',
      'Los Angeles',
      'New York',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'New York',
  },

  {
    question: 'What is Gamora\'s sisters name?',
    answers: [
      'Stacy',
      'Nebula',
      'Pepper',
      'Salty',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Nebula',
  },

  {
    question: 'How does one acquire the soul stone?',
    answers: [
      'Hit a game winning shot in overtime',
      'Be Black Panther',
      'Kill someone you love',
      'Steal the arc reactor from Iron Man',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Kill someone you love',
  },
  
  {
    question:'How did Starlord defeat Ronan the Accuser in \'Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 1\' ?',
    answers: [
      'Dance-off',
      'Spelling Bee',
      'Foot Race',
      'Staring Contest',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Dance-off',
  },

  {
    question: 'What is Thor the god of?',
    answers: [
      'Death',
      'War',
      'Thunder',
      'Mischief',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Thunder',
  },

  {
    question: 'What is Tony Stark\'s occupation?',
    answers: [
      'Genius Billionaire',
      'Philantropist',
      'Playboy',
      'All of the above',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'All of the above',
  },

  {
    question: 'Wakanda?',
    answers: [
      'Forever',
      'Sometimes',
      'On Fridays',
      'Every other day',
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Forever',
  },
];